export const questions=[
    {
        id:1,
        question:'How can I register for the upcoming student event?',
        answer:'To register for the event, simply visit our event registration page on our website. Follow the instructions, fill in the required information, and submit the registration form.',
    },{
        id:2,
        question:'Is there a registration fee for the student event?',
        answer:'The registration fee, if any, will be clearly mentioned on the event details page. Some events may be free, while others may have a nominal fee to cover costs. Please check the event information for specific details.',
    },{
        id:3,
        question:'Can I register on the day of the event?',
        answer:' While we encourage early registration, some events may allow on-site registration. However, availability is not guaranteed, and it is advisable to register in advance to secure your spot.',
    },{
        id:4,
        question:'What information do I need to provide during the registration process?',
        answer:'The required information may vary for each event, but typically, you will need to provide your full name, contact details, student ID (if applicable), and any other specific details mentioned in the registration form.',
    },{
        id:5,
        question:'How will I receive confirmation of my registration?',
        answer:'Upon successful registration, you will receive a confirmation email containing important details about the event, including date, time, venue, and any additional instructions. Please ensure your provided email address is accurate.',
    },{
        id:6,
        question:'Can I modify my registration details after submission?',
        answer:'In most cases, you can make changes to your registration details by logging back into the registration portal. However, there may be a deadline for modifications, so it is recommended to check the event website or contact the organizers for specific information.',
    },{
        id:7,
        question:'What do I do if I did not receive a confirmation email after registration?',
        answer:' If you have not received a confirmation email, please check your spam or junk folder. If you still can not find it, contact the event organizers directly through the provided contact information on the event website to ensure your registration was successful.',
    },{
        id:8,
        question:'Is there a limit to the number of attendees for the event?',
        answer:'Event capacity varies, and some events may have limited space. It is advisable to register early to secure your spot. If there is a maximum capacity, it will be mentioned on the event details page.',
    },{
        id:9,
        question:'Can I cancel my registration if I can not attend the event?',
        answer:'Yes, you can usually cancel your registration, but there may be a deadline for cancellations. Check the event website or contact the organizers for their cancellation policy and instructions on how to proceed.',
    },{
        id:10,
        question:'Are there any perks for early registrants?',
        answer:'Some events may offer special perks, discounts, or exclusive access to those who register early. Check the event details for any early registration benefits and deadlines.',
    },
] 